Guide to the Adler hip hop archive, circa 1970-2013.
Adler hip hop archive
- Series II. Posters and Framed Items
  - Bill Adler and Cey Adams, September 22, 2008 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    Event / Title: DEFinition: The Art and Design of Hip Hop
    Notes: Book release promotional materials. Page of 9 stickers (one sticker has been cut from the page)
    Size: 14in. x 20in.
  - Bill Adler and Cey Adams; DJ Adrock and Chuck Chillout, September 30, 2008 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    Event / Title: DEFinition: The Art and Design of Hip Hop book release party
    Venue: Red Bull Space, New York, NY
    Notes: Book release promotional materials. Page of 4 postcard invitations. Double sided
  - Bill Adler and Cey Adams, October 16, 2008 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    Venue: Book release event poster. Barnes and Noble, New York, NY
    Size: 10.75in. x 14in.
  - Luther "Luke" Campbell, May 24, 2011 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    Event / Title: Mayor of Miami-Dade County
    Notes: Political poster. Signed.
    Size: 11.5in. x 17.5in.
  - Def Jam Rapstar, October 5, 2010 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    Notes: Advertisement for video game. 2 copies
  - Group show featuring 38 visual artists., April 13 - May 26, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    Event / Title: It's Bigger Than Hip Hop
    Venue: Rush Arts Gallery
    Notes: Poster for an art exhibit curated by Derrick Adams. 2 copies.
  - Matta, Rammellzee, Futura, and Phase 2, November 9 - December 12, 2012 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    Event / Title: Deep Space
    Venue: Joseph Nahmad Contemporary Gallery
    Notes: Booklet with description of the show and essay by Namo Librizzi
    Size: 11.5in. x 16in.
  - Darryl McDaniels (DMC), June 28, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    Event / Title: It's Like That: 20 Years of Run DMC-JMJ
    Venue: Headquarters
    Notes: Invitation poster for photography show - 50 Works/20 Photographer/20 Years
  - Ricky Powell, March 3-22, 2002 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    Event / Title: Art exhibition poster
    Venue: XLARGE and x'e
    Size: 14.25in x 20.25in.
  - Featuring 'Rev. Run' of Run-DMC, undated (Box 29, Folder 5)
    Event / Title: Phat Farm's "Phat Classic" Reparations Campaign
    Notes: Advertisement for Phat Farm's "Phat Classic" Reparations Campaign
    Size: 10.25in. x 14.25in.
  - Run-DMC, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    Event / Title: Run-DMC Sweepstakes for New Coke
    Notes: Advertisement
  - Style Wars, c. 2005 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    Notes: Poster for a DVD release of the 1982 movie
  - Dondi White, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    Event / Title: "Dondi White: Style Master General The Life of Graffiti Artist Dondi White"
    Notes: Book release poster
    Size: 12in. x 16.5in.
  - Bill Adler, Dr. Dre, Ed Lover, Run-DMC, Tone Loc, Ice Cube, February 1991 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    Event / Title: Rap: Portraits and Lyrics od a Generation of Black Rockers
    Size: 18in. x 24in.
  - Martha Cooper, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    Event / Title: Hip Hop Files: Photographs 1979-1984
  - Martha Cooper "Hip Hop Files: Photographs 1979-1984", October 2004 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    Notes: Book release advertisement.
    Size: 13in. x 28in.
  - Ice Cube, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    Event / Title: St. Ides Premium Malt Liquor
    Notes: Advertisement. He is wearing a "Street Knowledge Productions Inc." t-shirt
    Size: 17in. x 23.25in.
  - Run-DMC and Dr. Benjamin Hooks of the NAACP, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    Event / Title:
    Notes: "Got the right to vote and will elect" poster with NAACP. 2 copies.
    Size: 17in. x 26in.
  - Street Stars, The Black Underworld, undated (Box 29, Folder 6)
    Notes: Poster for 6 documentaries. "Game Over,"
    "The Larry Davis Story," "The Guy Fisher Story," "Scarface 4 Life,"
    "The Karlton Hines Story," and "The True Story of Jam Master Jay and his Death"
  - Universal Zulu Nation, undated (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Cowboy, Melle Mel, Scorpio, Dr. Who, Barry B, Mr. Magic (and his daughter Monique), Roxanne Shante', Doug E. Fresh, Wise, Run, Kid Creole, Rahiem, Delite, Fruitkwan, Chill Will, DMC, Jam Master Play, Papa Jam, Don Barron, D.J. Red Alert, Master Rob, D.B.C., Grandmaster Flash, undated (Box 29, Folder 7)
    Event / Title: Group photograph.
    Notes: Reverse has photo of two unnamed women artists
    Size: 16in. x 20.75in.
  - Fat Joe; DJ Kay Slay; DJ KMT; DJ Webstar; DJ Sly; DJ Adam; hosted by Crazy Sam, July 7, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    Event / Title: Rucker Park Teen Jam
    Venue: Rucker Park (New York, NY)
    Notes: Concert event poster.
    Size: 19in. x 25.5in.
  - Heavy D and the Boyz and Big Daddy Kane, undated (Box 29, Folder 7)
    Event / Title: "Rap Masters" poster
    Notes: Taken from an unknown magazine. 2 sided.
    Size: 14.75in. x 21.25in.
  - LL Cool J, Mellow Man Ace, Chubb Rock, Howie Tee, King Sun, Def Jef, Special Ed, Redhead Kingpin and the F.B.I., 3rd Bass, Young MC, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    Event / Title: Hip Hop Magazine
    Notes: LL Cool J poster on one side, photos and article on reverse.
    Size: 15in. x 21.75in.
  - Nice and Smooth, Chubb Rock, Heavy D, Special Ed, D.J. Bobcat, D.J. Snowman, Eric B. and Rakim, Biz Markie, Roxanne Shante, Spinderella, Salt and Pepa, February - March 1990 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    Event / Title: Serious Hip Hop Magazine
    Notes: Poster. Nice and Smooth are on the front, the other artists are on the reverse.
    Size: 15in. x 22in.
  - Outta Jamaica, Mr. Dutty Wine, Tony Matterhon, DJ Kenny, Strika 1, November 22, 2013 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    Event / Title: Girl's Call Thanksgiving Affair
    Venue: United Banquet Hall (Hartford, CT)
  - Run-DMC, Glass, Frost, February 23-24, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    Venue: Grand Central Station and West High Auditorium (Anchorage, Alaska)
    Size: 17in. x 22in.
  - Russell Simmons, Crazy Sam, DJ Clue, DJ KMT, DJ Scribble, Bobby Konders, DJ Shake, JW Red, DJ Shockwave, November 10, 2002 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    Event / Title: Ruckah Unity Jam
    Venue: Octagon (New York, NY) )
    Size: 18in. x 25in.
  - Ultimate III, I.Q., Fab 5 Freddy, Busy Bee, Fearless Four, Mantronics, Crush City and invited guests Starski, LL Cool J, Run-DMC, Masterdon, Whodini, Fat Boys, Sparky D, Melle Mel, Roxanne Shante, Strafe, Educated Rapper, Coldcrush, Divine Sounds, Force MDs, March 29 - April 7, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    Event / Title: Roman, Amy and the Toxy present
    Venue: The Roxy (New York, NY)
    Notes: Concert poster. 2 copies.
    Size: 17in. x 22.25in.
  - Lloyd Bank$, 2006 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    Event / Title: Rotten Apple
    Record Label: G-Unit Records
    Notes: Record release poster. Lloyd Bank$ Southside Queens G-unit. 2 copies.
  - Bun B featuring Pimp C, Lyfe Jennings, Lil Wayne, Rick Ross, Chamillionaire, David Banner, Junior Reid, 8 Ball and MJG, May 20, 2008 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    Event / Title: Trill
    Record Label: Rap-A-Lot
  - Busta Rhymes, LL Cool J, Missy Elliot, Mobb Deep, Q-tip, Noreaga, Flipmode, Squad Big Pun, Fat Joe, Cam'Ron, Mysonne, Cormega, Beatnuts, Hot Boys, Next, Cru, PA, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    Event / Title: Violator, the album
    Record Label: Violator Records
    Notes: Record release poster. 7 copies with different artwork
  - The Disposable Heroes of Hiphoprisy, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    Event / Title: "Television, The Drug of the Nation"
    Record Label: 4th and B'way and Island Records
    Notes: Single release poster. Signed by Michael Franti and Rono Tse.
  - Dre featuring Rick Ross, 2006 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    Event / Title: "Chevy Riding High" from the Album "The Trunk"
    Size: 18in. x 23.75in.
  - Eminem; Jay-Z; NAS; 50 Cent; Rakim; Xzibit; D12; Obie Trice, 2002 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    Event / Title: 8 Mile Soundtrack
    Record Label: Shady Records
  - Ghostface Killah, 2006 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    Event / Title: Fishscale
    Notes: Record release poster. 2 copies.
  - G-Unit, September 20 - November 26, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    Event / Title: G-Unit Footwear by Reebok
    Notes: Advertisement poster.
  - Jim Jones. Hosted by Dame Flash, undated (Box 29, Folder 8)
    Event / Title: Harlem's American Gangster
    Record Label: Koch Records
  - KRS-One and Buckshot, September 15th (Box 29, Folder 8)
    Event / Title: Survival Skills
    Record Label: Duck Down Records
  - Lil John and the East Side Boyz, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    Event / Title: Crunk Juice
  - Lil Keke, 2008 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    Event / Title: Loved by Few, Hated by Many
    Size: 9in. x 24in.
  - Joeski Love, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    Event / Title: Joe Cool
    Record Label: Columbia
    Size: 23in. x 23in.
  - Nelly, 2002 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    Event / Title: Nellyville
  - Nelly, 2008 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    Event / Title: Brass Knuckles
  - R. Kelly, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    Event / Title: Happy People/U Saved Me
  - Rick Ross featuring John Legend, Kanye West, Lil Wayne, and T-Pain, 2009 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    Event / Title: Deeper Than Rap
  - Run-DMC, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    Event / Title: Together Forever: The Greatest Hits 1983-1991
    Record Label: Profile Records
  - Beanie Sigel, undated (Box 29, Folder 8)
    Event / Title: The Truth
  - Sisqo, undated (Box 29, Folder 8)
    Event / Title: Unleash the Dragon
  - Umar Bin Hassan, February 8, 2002 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    Event / Title: Life is Good
    Record Label: Stay Focused Records
    Notes: Record release poster. Signed by artist
  - Will C., 2008 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    Event / Title: Down the Dial
    Record Label: Double You Productions
  - Bill Adler and Cey Adams, October 16, 2008 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    Venue: Barnes and Noble (New York, NY)
    Notes: Book release poster.
    Size: 21.5in. x 27.75in.
  - The Diplomats, 2003 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    Event / Title: Diplomatic Immunity
    Record Label: Roc-a-Fella
    Notes: Record Release poster. 2 sided
    Size: 19.5in. x 27in.
  - The Force M.D.s, C. 1984 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    Event / Title: Love Letters
    Size: 20in. x 27in.
  - Looking at Music 3.0, February 16 - June 6, 2011 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    Venue: Museum of Modern Art (MOMA)
    Notes: Museum show poster.
    Size: 22in. x 28in.
  - Queen Latifah, February 8, 2010 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    Event / Title: Cover girl
    Notes: Advertisement from the New York Times
    Size: 22in. x 24in.
  - The Real Roxanne, c. 1984 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    Event / Title: The Real Roxanne
    Record Label: Select Records
    Size: 18in. x 27in.
  - Run-DMC; Runny Ray; Butter Luv, Cool T; Alyson Williams; Jellybean Benitez; DJ Hurricane; Larry Smith; Jam Master Jay; Lou Reed; Jim Carroll; Kurtis Blow; Dexter King (Box 29, Folder 9)
    Event / Title: Laminated Run-DMC photos from 1983-1985, 1995, 1999
    Venue: Lola's; Disco Fever; Danceteria; The Roxy; Universal Amphitheater
    Notes: Collage of color photocopies of Run-DMC at various musical venues, first album cover and first promotional photo.
    Size: 22in. x 25in.
  - Snoop Dogg and Bishop Don Juan, 2003 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    Event / Title: Very Select Original Premium (VSOP) Passion Blend
    Notes: Advertisement.
    Size: 18in. x 26in.
  - Eminem featuring 50 Cent, Obie Trice; D-12; Stat Quo; Cashis; Bobby Creekwater, December 5, 2006 (Mapcase-folder 1)
    Event / Title: The Re-Up
    Size: 24in. x 36in.
  - Jim Jones, November 7 (Mapcase-folder 1)
    Event / Title: "We Fly High (Ballin')"
  - Nas, December 19, 2006 (Mapcase-folder 1)
    Event / Title: Hip Hop is Dead
    Record Label: Def Jam Recordings/Columbia Records
    Notes: Record release poster. 3 copies.
    Size: 24in. x 35.5in.
  - Rick Ro$$, 2006 (Mapcase-folder 1)
    Event / Title: Port of Miami
  - Too $hort, August 29, 2006 (Mapcase-folder 1)
    Event / Title: Below the Whistle
    Record Label: Up All Nite/Jive Records
  - T-Pain; featuring Lil Wayne; Ludacris; Chris Brown, November 11, 2008 (Mapcase-folder 1)
    Event / Title: Thr33 Rings
  - Beastie Boys, 1987 (Mapcase-folder 2)
    Event / Title: License to Ill
    Notes: Mass market poster with image from album. 2 copies
  - Egotrip, July 16-August 21, 2004 (Mapcase-folder 2)
    Event / Title: Made You Look…Back: Ten Years of ego trip Photography
    Venue: Eyejammie Fine Arts Gallery, New York, New York
    Notes: Poster for a photography show. 2 copies.
  - Eric B. and Rakim, 1988 (Mapcase-folder 2)
    Event / Title: Follow the Leader
    Record Label: Uni Records
  - LL Cool J, 1986 (Mapcase-folder 2)
    Notes: Mass market poster.
  - LL Cool J, 1987 (Mapcase-folder 2)
  - Public Enemy, 1987 (Mapcase-folder 2)
  - Snoop Dogg, December 8, 2009 (Mapcase-folder 2)
    Event / Title: Malice in Wonderland
    Record Label: Doggystyle and Priority Records
  - UGK, December 19, 2006 (Mapcase-folder 2)
    Event / Title: Underground Kings
  - Beastie Boys, 1987 (Mapcase-folder 3)
    Notes: Def Jam poster using similar image to album. 2 copies.
    Size: 32.75in. x 42in.
  - Chaka Khan; LL Cool J; Kurtis Blow; Fat Boys; Debbie Harry; Sheila E.; Beastie Boys; Gap Band; Force M.D.'s; Run-DMC; Krush Grove, 1985 (Mapcase-folder 3)
    Event / Title: Krush Groove: Music from the Original Motion Picture Soundtrack
    Notes: Movie soundtrack poster. 3 copies
    Size: 27in. x 41in.
  - Public Enemy, 1988 (Mapcase-folder 3)
    Event / Title: It Takes a Nation of Millions to Hold Us Back
    Size: 30in x 46in.
  - Run-DMC, 1987 (Mapcase-folder 3)
    Event / Title: Special Issue of Penthouse Magazine poster
    Notes: 2 copies.
    Size: 29.25in. x 45in.
  - Run-DMC featuring Beastie Boys; Slick Rick; Public Enemy, 1988 (Mapcase-folder 3)
    Event / Title: Tougher Than Leather
    Notes: Movie poster
  - Run-DMC and Bill Adler, 1988 (Mapcase-folder 3)
    Event / Title: Tougher Than Leather: The Whole Uncensored Story! By Bill Adler book
    Notes: Uncut sheet of 8 book covers
    Size: 20.5in. x 30in.
  - 360 hip-hop.com - "I am not Hip-Hop", undated (Mapcase-folder 3)
    Notes: Advertisement. Uses image of Rudy Guliani
    Size: 30.5in. x 46in.
  - Disposable Heroes of HipHoprisy, 1992 (Mapcase-folder 4)
    Event / Title: "Television, The Drug of a Nation"
  - DMC, Russell Simmons, Missy Elliot, Bobbito Garcia, Grandmaster Caz, Doze, Futura 2000, Stash, Bonz Malone, Demon Dash, DJ Clark Kent, 2005 (Mapcase-folder 4)
    Event / Title: Just for Kicks
    Notes: Movie poster in Japanese
    Size: 20.25in. x 28.5in.
  - DMC, Russell Simmons, Missy Elliot, Bobbito Garcia, Grandmaster Caz, Doze, Futura 2000, Stash, Bonz Malone, Demon Dash, DJ Clark Kent, 2005 (Mapcase-folder 4)
    Notes: Movie poster. 3 copies.
  - Dream Warriors, 1991 (Mapcase-folder 4)
    Event / Title: And Now the Legacy Begins
    Notes: Debut album poster.
    Size: 19.5in. x 30in.
  - 50 Cent, undated (Mapcase-folder 4)
    Event / Title: "I am what I am" Reebok advertisement
  - Flav-a-Flav featuring No Self Control and the Band, 1991 (Mapcase-folder 4)
    Event / Title: Son of Bazerk
    Record Label: MCA
    Size: 24in. x 24in.
  - Paris, 1992 (Mapcase-folder 4)
    Event / Title: Sleeping with the Enemy
    Record Label: Guerrilla Funk
    Size: 24in. x 37in.
  - Run, undated (Mapcase-folder 4)
    Event / Title: Phat Farm Footwear advertisement
  - Run DMD; Fat Boys and the Human Beat Box; Kurtis Blow; Newcleus; Whodini, Mag Force/Swatch Breakers; Fantastic Duo Breakers; The Uptown Express Breakers, 1984 (Mapcase-folder 4)
    Event / Title: Fresh Festival '84
    Notes: Concert event poster. 2 copies.
  - Run-DMC, 1990 (Mapcase-folder 4)
    Event / Title: Back from Hell
    Size: 24in. x 35in.
  - Russell Simmons, Friday, October 21 (Mapcase-folder 4)
    Event / Title: Def Jam Recordings book signing
    Notes: Book signing event poster.
    Size: 22in. x 27.75in.
  - Snoop Dogg; DMC; Mobb Deep; Raekwon; De La Soul; Jim Jones; Papoose; M.O.P.; Everlast featuring DJ Muggs; Q-tip; Dead Prez; Kid Capri; Marley Marl; DJ KaySlay, November 29, 2007 (Mapcase-folder 4)
    Event / Title: 2007 J.A.M. Awards and Concert
    Venue: Hammerstein Ballroom (New York, NY)
  - Wiz Khalifa, September - October 2012 (Mapcase-folder 5)
    Notes: Poster pulled from unknown magazine.
    Size: 23in. x 32.5in.
  - Afrika Bambaataa; Ray Barretto; Stiv Bator; Pat Benatar; Big Youth; Ruben Blades; Kurtis Blow; Bono; Duke Bootee; Jackson Browne; Ron Carter; Clarence Clemmons; Jully Cliff; George Clinton; Miles Davis; Will Downing; Bob Dylan; The Fat Boys; Peter Gabriel; Peter Garrett; Bob Geldof; Daryl Hall; Herbie Hancock; Nona Hendrix; Linton Kwesi Johnson; Stanley Jordon; Kashif; Eddie Kendrick; Little Steven; Darlene Love; Malopoets; Grandmaster Melle Mel; Michael Monroe; John Oates; Sonny Okosuns; Bonnie Raitt; Joey Ramone; Lou Reed; Keith Richards; David Ruffin; Run-DMC; Scorpio; Gil Scott-Heron; Shankar; Bruce Springsteen; Zak Starkey; Ringo Starr; Tina B; Pete Townshend; Via Afrika; Tony Williams; Peter Wolf; Bobby Womack; Ron Wood, 1985 (Mapcase-folder 5)
    Event / Title: Sun City: Artists Against Apartheid
    Record Label: Manhattan/Capitol Records
    Notes: Record release album.
  - David Banner featuring Lil' Flip; Lil' Jon, May 20, 2003 (Mapcase-folder 5)
    Event / Title: Mississippi
    Size: 24in.x 36in.
  - Kurtis Blow, 1985 (Mapcase-folder 5)
    Event / Title: America
    Record Label: Mercury Records
    Size: 22in. x 33in.
  - De La Soul, undated (Mapcase-folder 5)
  - DJ Jazzy Jeff and the Fresh Price, 1987 (Mapcase-folder 5)
    Event / Title: Rock the House
  - Isis, 1990 (Mapcase-folder 5)
    Event / Title: Rebel Soul
    Record Label: M S Distributing Co.
  - Monie Love, 1990 (Mapcase-folder 5)
    Event / Title: Down to Earth
    Record Label: Warner Brothers
    Size: 23in. x 35in.
  - Run-DMC, 1985 (Mapcase-folder 5)
    Event / Title: King of Rock
    Notes: 3 copies.
  - Run-DMC, 1985 (Mapcase-folder 5)
    Event / Title: Krush Groove
    Notes: Movie soundtrack poster
  - Run-DMC; Juice Duce MC's; Elimination Squad; Wayne and Charlie; Fly TY and Tee-Y; D.S.C. Homeboys, 1985 (Mapcase-folder 5)
    Event / Title: Steve Lucas presents Spring Festival '85
    Venue: Mid-Hudson Civic Center (Poughkeepsie, NY)
  - Salt-N-Pepa, undated (Mapcase-folder 5)
    Size: 20in. x 34in.
  - Russell Simmons, November 2, 2010 (Mapcase-folder 5)
    Event / Title: "Running Russell Simmons"
    Notes: Advertisment.
  - Stetsasonic, 1988 (Mapcase-folder 5)
    Event / Title: In Full Gear
  - 2 in a Room, 1991 (Mapcase-folder 5)
    Event / Title: Wiggle It
    Record Label: Charisma Records
  - Whodini featuring Mille Jackson, 1987 (Mapcase-folder 5)
    Event / Title: Open Sesame
    Size: 20in. x 36in.
  - Public Enemy, undated (Mapcase-folder 6)
    Event / Title: 911 is a Joke
    Size: 40in. x 60in.
  - Whodini, c. 1984; 1
    Event / Title: Platinum Record Award
    Notes: Awarded to Def Jam Recordings to Commemorate the sale of 1,000,000 copies of the Jive/Artista Records album "Escape
  - Beastie Boys, 1986; 2
    Event / Title: Gold Record Award
    Notes: Awarded to Lyor Cohen to Commemorate the sale of 500, 000 copies of the Def Jam/Columbia Records album "Licensed to Ill"
  - Beastie Boys, 1986; 3
    Notes: Awarded to Russell Simmons to Commemorate the sale of 500, 000 copies of the Columbia Records album "Licensed to Ill"
  - Oran "Juice "Jones, c. 1986; 4
    Notes: Awarded to Russell Simmons to Commemorate the sale of 500,000 copies of the Def Jam/Columbia Records album "Juice" and the Gold Single "The Rain"
  - Whodini, c. 1986; 5
    Notes: Awarded to Lyor Cohen to Commemorate the sale of 500, 000 copies of the Artista album "Back in Black"
  - Eric B. and Rakim, 1987; 6
    Notes: Awarded to Bill Adler to Commemorate the sale of 500,000 copies of the 4th and Broadway Records album "Paid in Full"
  - Eric B. and Rakim, 1987; 7
    Notes: Awarded to Lyor Cohen to Commemorate the sale of 500,000 copies of the 4th and Broadway Records album "Paid in Full"
  - D.J. Jazzy Jeff and the Fresh Prince, c. 1987; 8
    Notes: Awarded to Lyor Cohen to Commemorate the sale of 500,000 copies of the Jive/RCA Records album "Rock the House"
  - D.J. Jazzy Jeff and the Fresh Prince, c. 1987, 1988; 9
    Notes: Awarded to Lyor Cohen to Commemorate the sale of 1,000,000 copies of the Jive/RCA Records album "He's the DJ, I'm the Rapper"
  - Public Enemy, 1987; 10
    Notes: Awarded to Bill Adler to Commemorate the sale of 500,000 copies of the Def Jam/Columbia Records album "Yo! Bum Rush the Show"
  - Public Enemy, 1987; 11
    Notes: Awarded to Lyor Cohen to Commemorate the sale of 500,000 copies of the Def Jam/Columbia Records album "Yo! Bum Rush the Show"
  - Bruce Springsteen, The Pretenders, John Cougar Mellencamp, Sting, and others, 1987; 12
    Notes: Awarded to Bill Adler to Commemorate the sale of 1,000,000 copies of "A Very Special Christmas"
  - Public Enemy, 1987-1988; 13
    Notes: Awarded to Bill Adler to Commemorate the sale of 1,000,000 copies of the Def Jam/Columbia Records album "It takes a Nation of Millions to Hold Us Back"
  - Public Enemy, 1987-1988; 14
    Notes: Awarded to Lyor Cohen to Commemorate the sale of 1,000,000 copies of the Def Jam/Columbia Records album "It Takes a Nation of Millions to Hold Us Back"
  - Slick Rick, 1988; 15
    Notes: Awarded to Russell Simmons to Commemorate the sale of 500,000 copies of the Def Jam/Columbia Records album "The Great Adventures of Slick Rick"
  - Slick Rick, 1988; 16
    Notes: Awarded to Lyor Cohen to Commemorate the sale of 1,000,000 copies of the Def Jam/Columbia Records album "The Great Adventures of Slick Rick"
  - De La Soul, c. 1989; 17
    Notes: Awarded to Lyor Cohen to Commemorate the sale of more than 1,000,000 copies of the Tommy Boy Music album "3 Feet High and Rising"
  - D.J. Jazzy Jeff and the Fresh Prince, 1989; 18
    Notes: Awarded to Lyor Cohen to Commemorate the sale of 100,000 copies of the Jive album "He's the DJ, I'm the Rapper"
  - EPMD, 1989; 19
    Notes: Awarded to Lyor Cohen to Commemorate the sale of 500, 000 copies of the Fresh Records album "Unfinished Business"
  - Ghostbusters II, c. 1989; 20
    Notes: Awarded to Lyor Cohen to Commemorate the sale of 500, 000 copies of the MCA Records album "Ghostbusters II"
  - Big Daddy Kane, 1989; 21
    Notes: Awarded to Rush Artist Management to Commemorate the sale of 500,000 copies of the Cold Chillin' Records album "It's a Big Daddy Thing"
  - LL Cool J, c. 1989; 22
    Event / Title: Platinum and Gold Sales Award
    Notes: Presented to Bill Adler to commutate the sale of 100, 000 copies of the album "Walking with a Panther" and 500,000 copies of the single "I'm that type of guy"
  - Alyson Williams, 1989; 23
    Notes: Awarded to Rush Artist Management to recognize sales in the United Kingdom of 100,000 copies of the Def Jam Recordings album "Raw"
  - D.J. Jazzy Jeff and the Fresh Prince, 1990; 24
    Notes: Awarded to Russell Simmons to Commemorate the sale of 50,000 copies of the Jive album "And in this Corner..."
  - Terminator X, Nikki D, EPMD, 3rd Bass, Public Enemy, LL Cool J, 1991; 25
    Event / Title: Rush Associated Labels - 16 Weeks at Number 1
    Notes: Presented to Lyor Cohen in appreciation of your part in helping RAL achieve the most #1 hits of any label in 1991
  - Anthrax, 1991; 26
    Notes: Awarded to Bill Adler to Commemorate the sale of 500,000 copies of "Attack of the Killer B's"
  - Juice, 1992; 27
    Notes: Awarded to Rush Artist Management to Commemorate the sale of 500, 000 copies of the Motion Picture Soundtrack
  - Mo'Money Soundtrack, 1992; 28
    Notes: Awarded to Russell Simmons-Rush Management to Commemorate the sale of 1,000,000 copies of the Perspective Records album "Mo'Money"
  - In the Beginning…there was rap, c. 1997; 29
    Notes: Awarded to Lyor Cohen to Commemorate the sale of 500, 000 copies of the Tone-Cool Records album "In the Beginning…there was rap"
  - Susan Tedeschi, c. 1998; 30
    Notes: Awarded to Lyor Cohen to Commemorate the sale of 500, 000 copies of the Tone-Cool Records album "Just Won't Burn"